<resources>
    <string name="translator_name"></string>

    <string name="app_name">Lunary</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Lunary</string>

    <string name="fab_scan">Scan Address / Key</string>
    <string name="fab_add_watch">Add Watch Only Wallet</string>
    <string name="fab_add_aswatch">Add as Watch Only Wallet</string>
    <string name="fab_gen_new">Generate New Wallet</string>
    <string name="fab_request">Request</string>
    <string name="fab_send">Send</string>
    <string name="fab_sendether">Send Ether</string>
    <string name="fab_setwalletname">Set Wallet Name</string>
    <string name="drawer_import">Import Wallets</string>
    <string name="drawer_about">About Us</string>
    <string name="drawer_donate">Donate</string>

    <string name="fr_price_current_price">Current Price</string>
    <string name="fr_wallet_overall_balance">Overall Balance</string>
    <string name="fr_detail_acc_balance">Account Balance</string>

    <string name="main_ac_wallet_added_suc">Your wallet was added successfully</string>
    <string name="main_ac_wallet_added_er">Wallet was already added</string>
    <string name="main_ac_wallet_added_fatal">Err Not a valid ethereum address</string>
    <string name="detail_acc_name_changed_suc">Wallet successfully renamed</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Show zero amount transactions</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Whether to hide contract calls without any ether amount or not</string>


    <string name="pref_title_start">Wallet as default tab</string>
    <string name="pref_sum_start">If enabled the app will start preselected in the wallet tab instead of the price tab</string>

    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Notification Sync</string>
    <string name="pref_sum_sync_frequency">Sync interval to check for new transactions</string>

    <string name="pref_currencys_title">Display Currency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_currencys">
        <item>USD</item>
        <item>EUR</item>
        <item>CHF</item>
        <item>GPB</item>
        <item>AUD</item>
        <item>CAD</item>
        <item>JPY</item>
        <item>RUB</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>2 hours</item>
        <item>4 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>8 hours</item>
        <item>16 hours</item>
        <item>24 hours</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>16</item>
        <item>24</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="notification_title">Transaction Received</string>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value" />

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">Incoming Transactions</string>
    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications_sum">Notify you about incoming transactions to any of your wallets</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_wallet_gen">Generate Wallet</string>

    <string name="prompt_email">Password</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Generate</string>

    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short (Min: 9)</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">Passwords do not match</string>

    <string name="generate_text">You are about to generate a new and encrypted offline wallet on this device. We recommend choosing a strong password in order to be able to ensure the best security possible for your funds. Please note that generating a strong and secure wallet is a highly compute-intensive task that can take up to several minutes! This process will be performed in the background so you can still use your phone as you usually would in the meantime. The progress is displayed in the notification bar of your device and as soon as we have finished generating your wallet, we will let you know.</string>

    <string name="import_text">You are about to import an unencrypted private key. We recommend choosing a strong password in order to be able to ensure the best security possible for your funds. Please note that importing a strong and secure wallet is a highly compute-intensive task that can take up to several minutes! This process will be performed in the background so you can still use your phone as you usually would in the meantime. The progress is displayed in the notification bar of your device and as soon as we have finished generating your wallet, we will let you know.</string>

    <string name="wallet_gen_service_title">Generating New Wallet</string>
    <string name="wallet_gen_service_title_import">Importing Wallet</string>
    <string name="choose_recipient_enterscan">Enter / Scan Recipient Address</string>
    <string name="choose_recipient_contacts">Or Choose Recipient from Address Book</string>

    <string name="choose_your_address">From</string>
    <string name="send_to">To</string>
    <string name="choose_ether_amount">Available Ether</string>
    <string name="choose_gas">Transaction Cost</string>


    <string name="request_activity_ether">Request Amount</string>
    <string name="request_activity_to">Your Wallets / Addresses</string>

    <string name="no_tx_history">This is the transaction overview showing all ether sent and received to and from other people. After adding a wallet and transferring some ether to it, the transaction and all future transactions will be displayed here.</string>
    <string name="no_wallet_history">You currently do not have any wallets. You can easily create or import one using the button below.</string>



    <string name="app_intro_text">Welcome to Lunary - the free and Open Source Ether Wallet for Android! Before starting, please take some time to read through our terms of service.</string>
    <string name="app_intro_title">Lunary Wallet</string>
    <string name="app_intro_please_agree">Please read and agree to the terms of service before proceeding</string>
    <string name="app_intro_iagree">I agree to terms of service</string>
    <string name="fragment_send_ether_amount">Ether Amount</string>
    <string name="fragment_send_cheaper">Cheaper</string>
    <string name="fragment_send_faster">Faster</string>
    <string name="fragment_send_total">Total</string>
    <string name="fragment_send_send_button">Send</string>
    <string name="fragment_recipient_hint_address">Address</string>
    <string name="fragment_recipient_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="fragment_detail_add_sharing">Address Sharing</string>
    <string name="fragment_detail_share_button">Share</string>
    <string name="walletgen_title">Generate Wallet</string>
    <string name="request_ether_title">Request Ether</string>
    <string name="qr_scan_title">QR Address</string>
    <string name="activity_send_title">Transaction</string>
    <string name="last_24_hours">Last 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="last_7_days">Last 7 Days</string>
    <string name="last_30_days">Last 30 Days</string>
    <string name="last_year">Last Year</string>
    <string name="err_no_con">No internet connection</string>
    <string name="wallet_menu_title">Wallet Settings</string>
    <string name="wallet_menu_changename">Change Wallet Name</string>
    <string name="wallet_menu_copyadd">Address to Clipboard</string>
    <string name="wallet_menu_export">Export Wallet</string>
    <string name="wallet_menu_delete">Delete Wallet</string>
    <string name="wallet_suc_exported">Wallet successfully exported</string>
    <string name="wallet_no_permission">Please grant write permission to export wallets</string>
    <string name="wallet_one_at_a_time">Not So Fast</string>
    <string name="wallet_one_at_a_time_text">We are currently generating a wallet for you, you can see the progress in your notification bar. Don\'t worry, we will notify you as soon as your wallet generation is finished :-) If you really wish to generate another one please wait for the current wallet to be completed first.</string>
    <string name="button_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="wallet_removal_title">ATTENTION: Wallet Removal</string>
    <string name="wallet_removal_sure">Are you sure you want to delete your watch only wallet?</string>
    <string name="wallet_removal_privkey">! THIS IS A WALLET WITH A PRIVATE KEY ! IF YOU HAVE NO BACKUP AND CONTINUE ALL YOUR ETHER ON THAT WALLET WILL BE LOST FOR EVER! ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO PROCEED? WALLET ADDRESS:</string>
    <string name="wallet_removal_last_warning">ARE YOU SURE? WALLET AND ALL COINS / TOKEN ON IT ARE GOING TO GET PERMANENTLY REMOVED. THIS IS THE LAST WARNING FOR WALLET:</string>
    <string name="button_yes">YES</string>
    <string name="button_no">NO</string>
    <string name="name_your_wallet">Name Your Wallet</string>
    <string name="button_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="name_other_address">Name Other Address</string>
    <string name="trans_menu_title">Transaction Settings</string>
    <string name="trans_menu_changename">Change Address Name</string>
    <string name="trans_menu_viewreceiver">View Receiver Address</string>
    <string name="trans_menu_openinb">Open in Browser</string>
    <string name="trans_no_trans_found">No transactions found for this address.</string>
    <string name="err_send_not_enough_ether">Not enough Ether on that Address</string>
    <string name="err_send_invalidamount">Invalid Amount</string>
    <string name="err_send_noreceiver">No receiver specified</string>
    <string name="err_send_noamount">No amount specified</string>
    <string name="name_your_address">Name Your Address</string>
    <string name="name_this_address">Name This Address</string>
    <string name="addressbook_menu_title">Addressbook Settings</string>
    <string name="addressbook_menu_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="import_title">Import Wallet</string>
    <string name="import_button">Import</string>
    <string name="main_grant_permission_export">Please grant write permission to export Wallets</string>
    <string name="main_grant_permission_import">Please grant read permission to import Wallets</string>
    <string name="dialog_watch_only_title">Watch Only Address</string>
    <string name="dialog_importing_wallets_title">Importing Wallets?</string>
    <string name="dialog_importing_wallets_text">We have detected %1$d new wallet%2$s in our Lunary folder. Would you like to import: %3$s</string>
    <string name="dialog_ex_nofull_title">No Full Wallet</string>
    <string name="dialog_ex_nofull_text">Watch only wallets can not be exported.</string>
    <string name="dialog_exporting_title">Exporting your Wallet</string>
    <string name="dialog_exporting_text">A copy of your Ethereum wallet will be placed inside the folder \"Lunary\" in the root directory of your Android phone. Please note that other applications that run on your device can technically access any wallets that you have exported. Due to this, we highly recommend erasing all exported wallets from the Lunary folder as soon as you have finished backing them up.</string>
    <string name="dialog_nofullwallet">No Full Wallet</string>
    <string name="dialog_nofullwallet_text">In order to send funds you need a full wallet with a private key. Please generate or import one first.</string>
    <string name="dialog_no_wallets">No Wallets</string>
    <string name="dialog_no_wallets_text">In order to request funds you need a wallet or a watch only address.</string>
    <string name="dialog_no_wallets_found">No Wallets Found</string>
    <string name="dialog_no_wallets_found_text">Please place the wallet you want to import inside the Lunary folder and make sure it is correctly named. When importing from Mist or other desktop client you don\'t have to rename your wallet.</string>
    <string name="notification_ticker">Incoming Ether Transaction…</string>
    <string name="notification_transfersuc">Transfer successful</string>
    <string name="notification_transferfail">Transfer Failed</string>
    <string name="notification_transferingticker">Transferring Ether…</string>
    <string name="notification_transfering_title">Transferring Ether</string>
    <string name="notification_might_take_a_minute">This might take a minute</string>
    <string name="notification_wallgen_maytake">This may take a couple minutes</string>
    <string name="notification_wallgen_title">Generating Wallet…</string>
    <string name="notification_wallimp_title">Importing Wallet…</string>
    <string name="notification_wallgen_finished">Wallet Creation Finished!</string>
    <string name="notification_wallimp_finished">Wallet Import Finished!</string>
    <string name="notification_click_to_view">Click to view</string>
    <string name="ether_and_token">Ether and Token</string>

    <string name="tos"><![CDATA[
<p><h2>Terms and Conditions ("Terms")</h2></p>

<p>Last updated: May 28, 2017</p>

<p>Please read these Terms and Conditions ("Terms", "Terms and Conditions") carefully before using the Lunary Ether Wallet (the "Service") operated by Lunary Ether Wallet, Rehanced ("us", "we", or "our").

Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service.

By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service. This Terms & Conditions agreement is licensed by TermsFeed to Lunary Ether Wallet.</p>

<p><b>Links To Other Web Sites</b></p>

<p>Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by Lunary Ether Wallet.

Lunary Ether Wallet has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that Lunary Ether Wallet shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services.

We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third-party web sites or services that you visit.</p>


<p><b>ASSUMPTION OF RISK</b></p>

<p>You acknowledge and agree that there are risks associated with utilizing an app service including, but not limited to, the risk of failure of hardware, software, the risk of malicious software introduction, and the risk that third parties may obtain unauthorized access to information stored within your device. You acknowledge and agree that we will not be responsible for any communication failures, disruptions, errors, distortions or delays you may experience when using our app, however caused. We take no responsibility for and will not be liable for any losses, damages or claims arising from the use of our app, including, but not limited to, any losses, damages or claims arising from (a) passwords being "Bruteforced", (b) hardware failure or data loss, (c) forgotten passwords, (d) corrupted wallet files, (e) incorrectly constructed transactions or mistyped Ether addresses; or (f) unauthorized access to mobile applications, (g)"phishing," viruses, third-party attacks or any other unauthorized third-party activities. </p>

<p><b>SUSPENSION; TERMINATION </b></p>

<p>We do not and can not terminate your usage of this app or any of your wallets. However we are using a third party API called "Etherscan.IO" to fetch certain statistics like transaction history and account balances. This API is not provided by us and etherscan.io who reseveres its right through their terms of service to terminate any abuse of their API such as request spamming or similar. In case of termiantion from Etherscan.IO certain features of this app are not available to you any more such as fetching transaction histories and account balances. Your wallets and its funds aswell as basic app features like exporting your wallets and generating new ones will always be available to you regardless of an etherscan.io account termination or not. For more information about etherscan.io take a look at their terms of service here: <a href="https://etherscan.io/terms">https://etherscan.io/terms</a>
</p>

<p><b>Governing Law</b></p>

<p>These Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Austria, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.

Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have between us regarding the Service.</p>

<p><b>DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES </b></p>
<p>(a) TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, AND EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY PROVIDED TO THE CONTRARY IN A WRITING BY US, OUR SERVICES ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW. WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM, AND YOU WAIVE, ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT AS TO OUR SERVICES, INCLUDING THE INFORMATION, CONTENT AND MATERIALS CONTAINED THEREIN.</p>

<p>(b) YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT INFORMATION YOU STORE OR TRANSFER THROUGH OUR SERVICES MAY BECOME IRRETRIEVABLY LOST OR CORRUPTED OR TEMPORARILY UNAVAILABLE DUE TO A VARIETY OF CAUSES, INCLUDING SOFTWARE FAILURES, PROTOCOL CHANGES BY THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS, INTERNET OUTAGES, FORCE MAJEURE EVENT OR OTHER DISASTERS, SCHEDULED OR UNSCHEDULED MAINTENANCE, OR OTHER CAUSES EITHER WITHIN OR OUTSIDE OUR CONTROL. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR BACKING UP AND MAINTAINING DUPLICATE COPIES OF ANY INFORMATION YOU STORE OR TRANSFER THROUGH OUR SERVICES. </p>

<p><b>LIMITATION OF LIABILITY</b></p>

<p>EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE REQUIRED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL COMPANY, OUR DIRECTORS, MEMBERS, EMPLOYEES OR AGENTS BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF PROFITS OR LOSS OF DATA, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO NEGLIGENCE) OR OTHERWISE, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE OUR SERVICES OR THE COMPANY MATERIALS, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY DAMAGES CAUSED BY OR RESULTING FROM RELIANCE BY ANY USER ON ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM COMPANY, OR THAT RESULT FROM MISTAKES, OMISSIONS, INTERRUPTIONS, DELETION OF FILES OR EMAIL, ERRORS, DEFECTS, VIRUSES, DELAYS IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION OR ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, WHETHER OR NOT RESULTING FROM A FORCE MAJEURE EVENT, COMMUNICATIONS FAILURE, THEFT, DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO COMPANY’S RECORDS, PROGRAMS OR SERVICES. </p>

<p><b>Changes</b></p>

<p>We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will try to provide at least 30 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.

By continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, please stop using the Service.
</p>

<p><b>Contact Us</b></p>

<p>If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.</p>

<br/><br/>

<p><h2>Disclaimer</h2></p>

<p>Last updated: May 28, 2017</p>

<p>The information contained on http://rehanced.com website and mobile app (the "Service") is for general information purposes only.</p>

<p>Lunary Ether Wallet assumes no responsibility for errors or omissions in the contents on the Service.</p>

<p>In no event shall Lunary Ether Wallet be liable for any special, direct, indirect, consequential, or incidental damages or any damages or loss of profits whatsoever, whether in an action of contract, negligence or other tort, arising out of or in connection with the use of the Service or the contents of the Service. Lunary Ether Wallet reserves the right to make additions, deletions, or modification to the contents on the Service at any time without prior notice.</p>

<p>Your wallets and private keys generated by this app are only stored locally on your device. Should you lose your wallet or keys (f.e in case of a device malfunction, factory reset, loss, physical damages, viruses or malware on the device or any other interaction with your device that may directly or indirectly result in data loss or manipulation) we are not able to help you return your funds or restore your keys because we don\'t have that data. Everything wallet related is stored physically on your device and only on your device. We are not liable for any loss of coins ("ether") or tokens in any of above mentioned cases or malfunction of our service or harmfull apps by third parties.</p>


<p><h2>Privacy Policy - Lunary Ether Wallet</h2></p>

<p><b>Data protection</b></p>

<p>We do not collect or save any of your private data by ourself as we do not communicate with a server owned by us. Information just as account balances, transaction histories and other similar to Ethereum related information are part of a public available and distributed ledger called "Blockchain". This information is not stored by us on any of our servers, the mentioned information is fetched from this Blockchain via a third party service called etherscan.io. You also agree to this etherscan.io privacy policy as found here: <a href="https://etherscan.io/terms">https://etherscan.io/terms</a>
We use the etherscan.io service to fetch Blockchain information and use it to display it to you via our app. Your Wallets, including its private keys, which are generated by this app are stored only locally on your device and are never shared or transmitted via web.
If there are further questions please don\'t hesitate to contact us as we are happy to help you in this regard.
For app usage statistics we use Google Analytics. More details about Google Analytics can be found in the paragraph "Privacy Policy for the use of Google Analytics".</p>

<p><b>Privacy Policy for the use of Google Analytics</b></p>

<p>This app uses Google Analytics, an analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your device, to help analyze how users use it. The information generated about your use of this app (including your IP address) is sent to and stored at a Google server in the U.S.A. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this app for the purpose of evaluating your use of the app, compiling reports on activity for operators and providing them other services relating to app activity and usage. The IP-address, that your device conveys within the scope of Google Analytics, will not be associated with any other data held by Google. For more information about Google Analytics visit <a href="https://google.com/analytics/terms">https://google.com/analytics/terms</a></p>


<p>By using this application you agree to our Privicy Policy and the processing of the collected information by Google, according to the above mentioned purposes. If you do not consent to such processing, please do not further access or use our applications.
More details about this topic can be found in Google\'s Privacy Policies:
<a href="https://google.com/policies/privacy">https://google.com/policies/privacy</a> </p>

]]>
    </string>

</resources>
